It's time for another episode of Upgami. This time we will be talking with Maho Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory and Kirara Yonemura of Ochanomoto.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Akiyama, have shortened my hair for the first time in a while.
Cute.
Thank you very much.
I've always had long hair and I've been wanting to have a haircut ever since I joined Hello!
It takes a lot of courage and I haven't had my hair cut since I was born,
I had never had my hair cut since I was born, so I really wasn't sure what to do,
I was wondering what I should do, but Saori Onoda, a member of the group, had done hair toning about 2 or 3 years ago,
That's how I came to know about hair donation,
I wanted to donate my hair at least once in my life,
I wanted to donate my hair at least once in my life, so I decided to do it this time.
It's wonderful. It's so nice.
I'm so happy. But I feel like the way I dance and express myself has changed a bit,
It's fresh and fun every time.
So, what about you, Kiura-chan?
I, Yonemura, had the opportunity to hold the first Christmas event as a franchisee of Ocha-no-Ma.
First time, huh? How was it?
We all dressed up in Christmas costumes for the event,
I thought it was really cute, Christmas for the tea ceremony horses.
I thought it was really cute.
Really?
I saw the pictures.
They were so cute and looked great on everyone.
Thank you very much.
Then we went down to the audience and sang "Jingle Bells" at first.
It was the first time for Ocha-no-Ma to sing in the audience, so it was very fresh and fun.
But really, a Christmas event is only once a year.
I think it was a lot of fun to be a little more relaxed and spontaneous than usual because only our fans were there,
At the Subaru Factory Christmas event, we had a shuffle unit,
At the Subaru Factory Christmas event, we had a shuffle unit, and Yofurno performed a song by Bow,
She suggested that we should do it with a treasure chest. She suggested that we should perform with a boupei, and we performed with it on.
Is ho-pei a Christmas thing?
I don't know, but I think it was a very enjoyable Christmas event.
Sounds like fun.
Let's start with the making of the music video of Lisa Tiny World. Let's start with this time's Attakami, here, Small Lisa, Small World, Making of the Music Video Shooting.
Tiny Lisa's new single "Tiny World" was released on December 6, 2012. Here is a sneak peek into the making of the music video for Tiny Lisa's latest single, Tiny Lisa Tiny Lisa Tiny Lisa Tiny Lisa Tiny Lisa Tiny Lisa Tiny Lisa Tiny Lisa
lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa small lisa
Today we are shooting a small world music video!
It's not often that I get to shoot in such a big city.
It's rare for me to shoot in such a big city, so I feel like I'm being watched by a lot of people.
I hope we can have a good time filming!
I'll do my best!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
Okay, that's all for now.
Thank you very much.
Let's go to the studio.
Okay, yes.
Yay. Oh.
Okay, here we go. Here we go.
Here we go, yay, start!
Yes, cut!
Yes, Mashii desu!
It's done. Now the sound, please.
I'm living life to the fullest
In the dizzying days
Falling in love and falling down
Oh, such a lovely little world
I've never stood barefoot on the sand except when I go to the beach.
I haven't done it at all recently, so it's a nostalgic feeling.
I have to be careful with the way I walk, which is totally different from how I normally do it.
I'll be careful and do my best.
Okay, are you ready?
Let's get started!
Yes, sir.
You're a little early.
Cut.
Almost there. It's a little worse than that.
Start.
In the wind, I'm going to raise my hand and swing my body at the tip of my toes over here in a rapid ㎏ sharp call hand position and say 'stand I have to lower my hand to make my legs goowe.
?
I don't know what changed when he said 'I have to lower my hand to make my legs goowe.
I don't know what changed when he said, but he needs to take his time with body practice.
Thank you for watching.
I look up at the sky.
King rises up.
BRAVO.
Okay, good.
ni
A great future.
But from you I thought
I'm missing a thing or two.
Who wouldn't want that?
A great future
But from you, I thought
I don't want to think about it.
I'm just living my life to the fullest
It's hard to see the day to day
Falling in and out of love
Oh, such a lovely little world
Yes, yes, yes
Yes, sir!
We've just finished shooting the music video for "A Small World"!
I think the highlight of this song is the scene in the desert.
We did a lot of different movements, so I'm looking forward to seeing how the music video turned out.
I'm looking forward to seeing how it turned out.
And in the scene where they walk around the city, they wear trench coats and so on.
I was conscious of walking around Shibuya in a cool and mature way.
I hope people will pay attention to that.
This song goes back and forth from a big scale story to a small everyday story.
The back and forth in the lyrics is very interesting.
I also think that as I sing the song. I'm also thinking about it as I sing.
I hope that you will listen to my songs and feel the joy and fun of them.
I hope that you will be able to hear and feel the joy and fun of this song.
I think I will have many more opportunities to sing in the future.
I'm sure there will be many more opportunities to sing in the future, so I hope that many of you will listen to it.
It was wonderful, wasn't it?
I've always loved Risa Ogata's eyes, and they are indeed beautiful.
Her eyes are a little brownish.
I always liked the way they shined when she appeared on camera.
I always thought they were so beautiful.
But in the music video, your eyes seem to sparkle a lot.
And the clothes she was wearing in the desert scene looked really good on her.
The music video has a very fragile feel to it.
I thought it had a lot of those elements in it.
It's a music video that makes you want to watch it over and over again.
I, Risa Ogata, also thought the world view was wonderful.
I thought the song seemed to be quite difficult to express.
But it was totally beautiful.
Just standing there, it was like a picture.
I was glued to the stage.
I thought it was really wonderful, with a view of the world that only Risa Ogata could bring out.
That's all for Risa Ogata, Small World, the making of the music video shooting.
Thanks for your hard work!
Thank you for all your hard work!
Next is here. Morning Musume。 23 Wake up call Waking up when you wake up Vocal recording
Morning Musume。 23's latest single, Wake Up Call Awake When You Wake Up, please take a look at the vocal recording of Honoo Okamura.
Okay, let's record them in order.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, let's go to the first A melody.
That kind of make-up doesn't suit you, it's an imposition of femininity that you can't wear.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I'm trying to say.
It's just that... it's pretty... it's probably best if it's thick.
I don't want it too thin.
I'm trying to keep it as thick and cool as possible.
And a little bit rock 'n' roll.
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you. It's an imposition of femininity that can't be erased.
Let's do it in a kind of "I can't erase my femininity" kind of way.
That kind of makeup doesn't suit you. It's an imposition of femininity that you can't wear. You don't look good in that makeup. It's an imposition of femininity that you can't wear.
I'm not doing it for you. That's all I'm trying to say.
I think it's good. Then I'll tell it to my juniors.
It's not for you, that's all I'm saying.
I'm not trying to be cute and cool, but I'm trying to be cute and cool, and I'm trying to be cute and cool.
I'm not trying to be cute, but I'm trying to be cool, and I'm trying to bruise it, and I'm trying to control it.
I'm just trying to be cute, but I'm a creature of mockery and deceit, and I have to affirm every face.
I just want a little more kick. - Okay.
Okay, I'm sorry.
And then something cool... a little cloud... ah, okay, bear.
accent on the head!
I'll try it with an accent on the head.
Unfortunately, it's not for you. That's all I want to say.
I'm just trying to be cute and cool and anxious.
we have to fix any face.
Okay, let's continue.
We're living creatures with a screen system. We have to fix every face.
I'm sure it's boring to be dictated to by others.
I don't want to deceive myself
Wake up! Goal!
Let's get a little rhythm going.
Yeah, it's cool to push back.
Let's try it again.
OK, I got it.
Okay, let's try the next one.
Next chorus.
I don't want to cheat
Make up goal It's time to wake up
Time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart
Just do it, Just do it, Just do it, Just do it
I'll shine the light on you
Dance free, dance free, dance free, dance free, dance free
That's me
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I'll shine the light on you
Yeah, you're such a softy
I want to be more, I want to be bold I want to be more... bold.
I know it's hard.
If it's not hard, you're not singing properly.
Yes, sir.
I don't want to deceive myself.
Wake up, Call! It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
The sun is in my heart
Just do it
Just do it! Just do it!
Dance baby Dance baby Dance baby Dance baby
Okay, let's continue.
Okay.
Once upon a time
In the depths of the night
In this heart at the end
Just do it Just do it Just do it Just do it
Someone's heart at the bottom of the night, waiting for morning
If I stay there, it's a little bit tasteless
So I'll wait for the morning, and then I'll take it out once and hit the morning again.
Let's try one more time
Someone's heart at the bottom of the night, waiting for morning, I'll give you my hand
Yeah, that's it.
Okay, I guess that's it.
Okay.
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much.
Well, it looks difficult. It looked really difficult.
You're really good at it. I mean, you can go high and low.
It's amazing that you can do it all so quickly.
I think you are a genius.
Very good!
Um, I really like your voice, Homare.
I don't know how to describe it... it's a little bit young and bright.
I really like your sweet voice.
But for this song, she was asked to use a thicker voice.
I thought her voice was fresh and nice, and this song is a bit addictive. I thought his voice was fresh and nice, and this song is a bit addictive.
I want to listen to it more and more and find many things I like about it.
That's all for Morning Musume。  That's all for Morning Musume's 23 Wake Up Call: When You Wake Up, a vocal recording by Hiroon Okamura.
Thank you for everything, and I'll be rooting for you too.
This is Shigeru Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory and Kirara Yonemura of Ochanomama.
Next up is Tsubaki Factory's "If you're only delusional, you're free" vocal recording.
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Marin Fukuda's song "Delusion Only Freedom" from Tsubaki Factory's latest single "Delusion Only Freedom"!
Let's see, the whole thing is already pretty flavorful
Yes, sir.
In terms of seasoning
Yes
Well, a little bit strong
I try to make it as comical as possible.
Yes.
Paid out with good things.
Tell me what's wrong with him, I don't want to know
In front of everyone, it's a posthumous, messed up love affair
Ideals always seem to hurt, I know, but...
I like the second half of the song.
It's a little more... comical, a little more...
I'm kind of on the cool side now, so...
I think it could be a little more interesting.
Paid out with a good word...
I'm going to make it so thick
Tell me what's wrong with it, I don't want to know
I can't think in front of everyone, my love is getting all messed up
I can't think in front of everyone, I want a messy love
I can't think in front of everyone, I want a love that's a mess
I'm always in pain, I know it's true, but...
I know, but it's nice, a little accent.
I know, I know, I know
I can't think in front of everyone, I can't think in front of everyone, I can't think in front of everyone
Fade out with no good things I'll let his words roll off my tongue
Tell me what's wrong with you, I don't want to know
I want to be able to sit in front of everyone and make love
Ideally, I always feel like a pain, I know it's true, but...
I know it's a pain in the ass, but I'm okay with it.
Okay, B melodyOkay, B-melody.
Ideals always hurt. I know it hurts.
Everyday, Everynight It's not an eternal romance
I don't think we should go any harder on Everyday.
I don't want to go too hard on the "Everyday.
Yeah, I'm just trying to make it a little bit more lively with the second line.
Everyday.
Empyretic
I'd like to make it a little bit less gutsy, and then I'd like to make it a little bit more
Roman's
Nah.
I'll try to make it a little bit more "sticky," "smoky flowery," "idol career change ondo," that kind of thing.
OK, I'll take it like that.
Okay, first chorus
There's no romance in it.
If you're just delusional, you're free
I'm older than you, I'm younger than you, I'm in love with you
If you're just delusional, then you're free
Even if you're strong and a princess
Sleeping maiden 1:30
I have to dream
Goo Night
Almost good
From the entrance of the Sleepy Maiden
Sleepy Maiden
Make the voice a little thicker
A little more rock
And I'll try to sing in a huff as much as possible
I don't have any romance.
If it's just a fantasy, it's freewheeling
I'm older than you, younger than you, lovey-dovey
If it's just a fantasy, then I'm free
Even if you're strong and a princess
Sleeping maiden 1:30
I have to dream
Goo Night
OK, let's modulate thenOK, so let's transpose it.
If you're just delusional, you're free
Even if you're a strong princess
Fantasy move me
I'm a prince, I'm a prince, I'm a prince, I'm a prince, I'm a prince
Lust, cowardice, let's blow it away
Jean Nooner Cinderella
Wake up maiden 1:30
Make My Dream Come True
Goo Night
second half good
I'm a prince love love love love
I'm a prince, I'm a prince, I'm a prince, I'm a prince, I'm a prince
I wonder if I'll turn there tightly
Awakening Maiden
I'll manage to change the nuance
Maiden 1:30
Make your dreams come true
Good night
It's the last one, so I want to make it strong.
Yeah, something like that.
Good night
OK, I'll start with this song.
Thank you very much.
Okay, that's it. Thank you for your hard work.
This song has a lot of quirks in a good way, and the way she sings is something that has never been done before, like a little thicker here and a little prettier there.
When I recorded the song, I thought it was very difficult to distinguish between the two.
I thought Marin was very good at changing the way she sang, and her face when she sang, she has this habit of closing her eyes.
I thought it was very cute. I thought it was very cute.
Yes, this song is really great, and when I saw Tsubaki Factory's performance, I felt like they were performing it lightly.
But when I listened to it like this, I realized that it is a very difficult song.
The key is really high, isn't it? Yes, it is very difficult because it suddenly gets very high.
But you sang it very well, so I was really impressed with you.
The music video is also quite interesting and fun to watch, so I watched it.
So I watched it. Everyone is dressed up in different ways. Yes! I would like you to see the cute music video, too. I saw it. Everyone is dressed up in different ways. Yes! I hope you will watch the cute music video too!
Well, that's all for now, Tsubaki Factory, if you're just delusional, this is the vocal recording of Freedom Marin Fukuda!
Thank you very much!
Anjurum Redline.
I like your hard work a lot.
It's time to say goodbye to Shigeru Akiyama and Kirara Yonemura!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time, but this is the last one for the year 2023, so how do you feel about this past year?
Well, in July, Ochanoma released a single called "Quattro English Name Single" which had 4 songs with English names, and it left a great impression on me.
I was very impressed with that single.
I spent a lot of time with the members, and I think it helped us strengthen our bond.
I'm going to listen to a lot of new songs.
Thank you very much.
I think we, Tsubaki Factory, had a lot of new challenges this year,
First of all, we started with a live band.
We have been dreaming of live performance for a long time, but we also had an overseas tour and the first graduation live for the graduating members.
I think that I have been able to take on many new challenges, and it is very important for me to speak out about my dreams.
I think it is very important to express our dreams out loud, so I would like to continue to express what I want to do in the next year.
Now, as this is the last live broadcast of 2023, we will not be broadcasting on January 8, 2024, and the next live broadcast will be on January 11 at 19:00.
UpCami will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UpFront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel to get a glimpse of what you don't normally see.
In this episode of UpCami, we are joined by Maasa Akiyama of Tsubaki Factory and Kirola Inouemura of Ocha-no-Ma.
Bye bye!
Next time on Upokami,
Angulum Life is Beautiful
The Making of the Music Video Shooting
And,
Juice! Juice! Bon voyage!
Please look forward to it!
Next notice